<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Journal</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sign_in_to_continue">Sign in to continue</string>
    <string name="action_add">Add</string>
    <string name="hint_title">Enter Note title here</string>
    <string name="hint_content">Enter Note content here</string>
    <string name="action_update">Update</string>
    <string name="create_or_add_dairy_title">Create or Add a Note</string>
    <string name="action_delete_note">Delete note</string>
    <string name="sample_note">A simple Timeline View that demonstrates the power of
        ConstraintLayout and RecyclerView. No drawing, just plug in and play. And this can only
        ConstraintLayout and RecyclerView. No drawing, just plug in and play. And this can only
        ConstraintLayout and RecyclerView. No drawing, just plug in and play. And this can only
        take 5 liens on the view holder, once it is more than 5 lines, it is truncated from the left hand side.</string>
    <string name="no_notes_available">No Notes yet, click the + icon to add notes</string>
    <string name="format_created_at">Created : %s</string>
    <string name="format_updated_at">Modified : %s</string>
    <string name="details_title">Details</string>
    <string name="sample_title">Android P Developer Preview Android P Beta is now available for Pixel devices and top devices from our partners. Install the beta on any supported device for testing and development or just to try Android P.  GET STARTED Make your apps compatible Run the preview on a Pixel device or Android Emulator, install your current app, and test where behavior changes may affect it.  Get Android P How to get Android P for your device or emulator  LEARN MORE Behavior changes System changes for apps on P  LEARN MORE Compatibility testing Easy steps to reach compatibility  LEARN MORE What\'s in Android P?</string>
    <string name="sample_note_content">Starting in Android 7.0 (API level 24), you could add an action to reply to messages or enter other text directly from a notification. Android P enhances this feature with the following enhancements:  Simplified support for conversation participants: The new Person class is used to identify people involved in a conversation, including their avatars and URIs. Many other APIs, such as addMessage(), now leverage the Person class instead of a CharSequence. The Person class also supports the Builder design pattern.  Support for images: Android P now displays images in Messaging Notifications on phones. You can use setData() on the message to display an image. The following code snippet demonstrates how to create a Person and a message containing an image.</string>
</resources>
